Josip Mužić

I am currently a student in my final year of the Web and Mobile Computing program at RIT Croatia, studying in Croatia's capital city Zagreb. When I graduate from RIT Croatia, I will receive a Bachelor of Science in Information Technology and I'm planning to move to England. I have a lot of experience with Flutter and React, alongside other technologies.

Ul. Dr. Luje Naletilića 150, Zagreb, 10000 Croatia +385 95 384 8499 josipmuzic99@gmail.com https://www.josipmuzic.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Best Technology, Zagreb - Flutter Developer

OCTOBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Made a single App that is available for Web/Android/iOS using Flutter. We used GraphQL to connect to the backend. This was a rather fun project for me because it was the first time I used GraphQL in a Flutter project. This ended up meaning that I didn't need to set up any kind of state management.

Bebabit, Zagreb - Full-Stack Developer

JUNE 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

I got scouted by a recruiter for a specific project. It was a project for a big client in Croatia called Unisport. They needed me to create a React PWA, Flutter app, and support the junior backend developer (Node.js).

Cinnamon Agency, Zagreb - Full-Stack Developer

MAY 2020 - MAY 2021

When I first came to Cinnamon I worked on a React project. After successfully completing that project and being eager to learn more, I was put on a project with technology unknown to me beforehand (Flutter). Towards the end of my career here I was mostly on Flutter projects, occasionally jumping back to Web projects.

RIT Croatia, Zagreb - Web and Mobile Computing Tutor

SEPTEMBER 2019 - MAY 2020

I held tutoring hours for students and my sessions were always full. Students came to me for help with the subject "Web and Mobile Computing", but also for other subjects.

Infomedica, Split — Software developer intern

MAY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

I used Angular to make a demo web-app of their already existing iRIS software.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Dart, Javascript, (HTML, CSS), PHP, Kotlin, Swift, Java, C#, Python

FRAMEWORKS

Flutter, React, Angular, Cordova, Node.js, Selenium

DBMS

MySQL, MsSQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, OracleDB

SKILLS

I am very skillful at using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator, as well as some other graphic design tools.

I am a big Linux enthusiast. I've been using various Linux distros since 2014.

SOFT SKILLS

Communication, Teamwork, Problem-Solving, Flexibility, Self-Motivation, Responsibility

ArsSacra, Međugorje — Full-Stack Developer

JANUARY 2019 - MAY 2019

I was in charge of creating an E-commerce store selling religious artifacts. I used Node.js and React. I did not implement any sort of payment service as I was too scared at the time to make anything involving money. Instead, the customers were told to Chat with the staff about what product they wanted, and then the transaction would be done through Paypal.

EDUCATION

RIT Croatia, Zagreb (Croatia) - Web and Mobile Computing

SEPTEMBER 2018 -

All my IT subjects I have successfully completed with the highest grades out of all of my peers. I have been on the Dean's list every year until now and I plan on continuing that until I graduate.

Grammar School (Gimnazija), Mostar (Bosnia and Herzegovina) and Music High School "Katarina Kosača" (Srednja glazbena škola "Katarina Kosača"), Mostar (Bosnia and Herzegovina)

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2018

I completed all four years with the highest grades in both high schools and participated in many competitions and concerts.

SOME PROJECTS

Unisport (Flutter, React, Node.js)

JUNE 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

Our task was to create a relatively big project but in a very short amount of time. My obligations consisted of making a Flutter App showing their data to their users (students, professors, sports enthusiasts), a React PWA to be used by admins to keep track of scores/events/teams in real-time, as well as supporting backend on various tasks.

BetContest (Flutter)

AUGUST 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021

This is an app I developed for a client of the company I worked for (Cinnamon Agency). It is a betting game application designed to play with friends. You bet with fake money and challenge your friends to see who will win. Aside from the challenge of this being my first real project in Flutter, I had the challenge of the backend starting later than me, so I had to predict a lot of things. A few of these included preparing the models without knowing what the models would look like, making them easily refactorable and expandable, and later returning to those places and adjusting them based on the implemented backend.

LANGUAGES

Bilingual: English, Croatian Additional language: Italian

HOBBIES

I enjoy playing the piano, ukulele, guitar, and clarinet. Some of my other hobbies include: jogging, video games, and cooking.

GoRide (React)

MAY 2020 - AUGUST 2020

This is a website I developed for a client of the company I worked for (Cinnamon Agency). It was a big project with a lot of people working on it. One big challenge was at the start getting into the code and working with code that a lot of people worked on. However, I was assigned a great mentor from whom I learned a lot.

iRIS (Angular)

MAY 2019 - AUGUST 2019

A company I worked for at the time already made a very successful *IRIS* software. They were using and selling it for years, but they decided to experiment with making a web-app. I used Angular to develop it, while also using their old app code-base as a guide.